{
    "subject": "resource/The_Hour_of_the_Pig",
    "predicate": "ontology/country",
    "object": "resource/France",
    "human_readable": "The Hour of the Pig is from France.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9818018078804016,
            "question": "Is The Hour of the Pig French in origin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9665543437004089,
            "question": "Is The Hour of the Pig a French creation?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9486055374145508,
            "question": "Is The Hour of the Pig a French work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8570743203163147,
            "question": "Could The Hour of the Pig be described as French literature?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7977086305618286,
            "question": "Where is The Hour of the Pig from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7396605610847473,
            "question": "What is the origin of The Hour of the Pig?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6851006746292114,
            "question": "What is the nationality of The Hour of the Pig?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6590768694877625,
            "question": "Where was The Hour of the Pig created?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6574603915214539,
            "question": "To which country does The Hour of the Pig belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5539785623550415,
            "question": "What is the country of production for The Hour of the Pig?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Hour of the Pig is from France.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3040_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which country does The Hour of the Pig belong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3040_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was The Hour of the Pig created?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3040_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the nationality of The Hour of the Pig?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3040_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3040_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3040_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3040_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3040_147.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3040_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3040_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3040_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3040_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3040_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3040_77.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe documents mention that \"The Hour of the Pig\" is set in 15th-century France, which supports the claim that it is a French film."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information that supports the claim that \"The Hour of the Pig\" is set in France, specifically in a rural village named Abb\u00e9ville, which is in northwestern France. Therefore, it can be concluded that the statement \"The Hour of the Pig is from France\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}